(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
Hololive Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
It's Ichijou Ririka!
I'm Mori Calliope!
ホロライブファンクラブ、始めました！
We've started the Hololive Fan Club!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや、チケット先行抽選。
Exclusive original goods and advance ticket lotteries.
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
Lots of other fun content too!
Campaigns too? That sounds really fun.
I'm curious.
さあみんな！ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Come on everyone! Let's have fun together in the Hololive Fan Club!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから、ずっと気になってたんだよね～！
I heard the open-air bath here is famous, so I've been curious about it for a long time!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
...Hey, won't you go with me?
えっ！？一緒に入るって意味じゃないよ！？
Eh!? I don't mean we get in together!?
おーそーじ！
Big, Big, Clean, Up!
モココ、大掃除やってみたいんだよね！
I want to try this "Big Cleanup" thing!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
And of course, you'll be joining me!
じゃあさっそく大掃除、開始だ～！
In that case, let the Big cleanup begin!
え～？服のすきまがどうしたって～？
Eh~? What about the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな～？
While I was cleaning, where on earth were you looking~?
お～！ここが夢にまで見た日本の温泉町～♪
Wow! I've always dreamed of going to Japan's hot springs districts!
ん？もしかして……私と一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
...what's that look? Are you hoping for the mixed one?
……いいよ、一緒に、入ろっか……？
...You know what? Sure, let's go there.
って、やばいやばい！
Wait, oh no oh no!
みんなそろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
Everyone, the countdown is starting soon!
５！
5!
４！
4!
３！
3!
２！
2!
１！
1!
０！
0!
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！
今年もよろしくお願いします！
I look forward to working with you this year too!
えへへ……なんか改めてかしこまると、恥ずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehe... somehow being formal like this makes me feel shy♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？
It's called Diamond Fuji, right?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えて来たよ！
Look, look! You can start to see the outline of Mt. Fuji!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ～！
Just seeing this scenery is so moving~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！
This is sudden, but I'll be making osechi!
つまみぐいしちゃだめだよ？
And no sneaking a bite, you hear?
もしつまみぐいしちゃったら……
If you do sneak a bite...
ガブってしちゃうからねっ！？
Bau wau! I'll take a big chomp out of you!
おめでとー！おめでとー！
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Celebrating while hugging you!
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
I'm the only one that can hug you, so other people can't copy this!
ほらほらキミもモココのことぎゅ～ってして！
C'mon, now it's your turn to hug me back!
せーの！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Ready, go! Please treat us well this year too!
再販！ゆくホロ2023！くるホロ2024！
Resale! Yuku Holo 2023! Kuru Holo 2024!
参加タレント一覧
List of Participating Talents
ホロ新春ゲーム祭 2026
Holo New Year Game Fes 2026
ときのそら Dreamy in Motion
Tokino Sora: Dreamy in Motion
ホロライブ3期生
Hololive 3rd Generation
次に挑む舞台は
The next stage we challenge is...
大作戦？
A Grand Strategy?
#きゅるるん大作戦
#KyururunGrandStrategy
最強アイドル、推ししかないでしょ
Strongest Idols, You Gotta Stan!
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで
Packed with 'Love' and 'Cute',
あなたと作る大作戦！
A Grand Strategy made with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、
All the 'up until now's,
ときめくような一瞬を！
And a heart-fluttering moment!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like we can go anywhere.
Oh yeah yeah
ちなみに作戦の内容は
By the way, the strategy details are:
とにかくかわいい
Just be cute!
かわいいに満たされろ
Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！
Strategy in progress!
#新春！3期生24時間配信
#New Year! 3rd Gen 24-Hour Stream
hololive DEV_IS 正月衣装お披露目リレー
hololive DEV_IS New Year Outfit Reveal Relay
音乃瀬 奏
Otonose Kanade
一条 莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭 らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟 はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
響咲 リオナ
Isaki Riona
虎金妃 笑虎
Koganei Niko
水宮 枢
Mizumiya Su
輪堂 千速
Rindo Chihaya
綺々羅々 ヴィヴィ
Kikirara Vivi
FLOW GLOW NEW VOICE PACK COMING SOON
まもなく配信開始します
Streaming starts soon.
This is FLOW GLOW...
...in Countdown Live.
来年もよろしく！
Let's have a great year next year too!
Let's go!
搭載 V8 Engine
Equipped with a V8 Engine,
第7感持ってる原人
a primitive man possessing the 7th sense.
Rockするこの世界と全身で
Rocking this world with my whole body,
この5人でGameはChange
with these five, the Game will Change.
唸る4輪発射せよ
Launch the roaring four wheels!
皆さんサンキュー散乱Halo
Thank you everyone, scattering Halo.
操る時代のハンドルを
Manipulating the steering wheel of the era,
Holo一番ここBrand Zero
Holo's number one, right here, Brand Zero.
Risk超えて挑戦
Overcoming Risk to challenge,
ChanceもSetだ当然
Chance is also a Set, naturally.
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the peak,
座布団積んで気象天？
stacking cushions to reach the high heavens?
飲み込む FG Roadster
Engulfing everything, FG Roadster.
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces gather, ability users.
この歴史治るどこか
Where will this history be fixed?
ぶっちぎりで置き去り拘束車
Leaving the restraints far behind at top speed.
今光速でぶち抜けていく大気圏
Now piercing through the atmosphere at light speed,
EngineからJetの炎入れている怪気炎
pouring Jet flames from the Engine, high spirits.
天界に広がる大地を超えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropic line spreading through the heavens and earth.
Back mirrorにBig Blueが映ってる I feel...
The Big Blue is reflected in the Back mirror, I feel...
Fire!
打ち明けたいから飛んでく打ち出せ帯
I want to reveal it so I'll fly, launch the zone.
この燃料朽ち果てないです
This fuel will never rot away.
銀河で寿司食べたい
I want to eat sushi in the galaxy!
見えてるでっかいVision
I can see a huge Vision,
燃えてるMember一同
all the Members are burning up.
只今現在進行形超えて世界規模
Right now, surpassing the present progressive form, global scale!
Come on 走らせ Star
Come on, run the Star!
心臓が Monster
My heart is a Monster.
Alien the terminal?
FG Party High
光る Tesla Roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster.
Heavy Booster 目覚めてく本能を
Heavy Booster, awakening instincts,
青い炎を
the blue flame.
We are back. Let's go out.
Targetの中ゼロから
Inside the Target, from zero,
空まで貫け
pierce through to the sky!
走る FG Roadster
Running FG Roadster,
唸る Booster Flow Glow
roaring Booster, Flow Glow.
The stage to be... 今 Chase me!
The stage to be... now Chase me!
顔つき習慣化？ Handle捌き急昇格？
Habitual expression? Handle handling sudden promotion?
爆走重症中バカ？
Explosive run, critically ill idiot?
次元が違うレンズ枠
Dimensionally different lens frame.
Corner攻めてのギリギリ
Attacking the Corner at the limit.
Motor全開ビリビリ
Motor full throttle, tingling.
空から導き
Guidance from the sky,
お肌がピチピチ
skin is fresh and bouncy.
タイヤ焦がして Donut Turn
Burning tires, Donut Turn.
弾け飛んでく Drum Can
Bursting and flying Drum Can.
お客さん速度高くてブチ上がってる枠たくさん
Customers, high speed and getting hyped, lots of frames.
ゼロから最高到達点
From zero to the highest point.
貯めてる太陽光発電
Saving up solar power generation.
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid,
超覚醒突入 Bonus Stage
Super awakening entry, Bonus Stage!
一直線伸びてる Road
Road stretching in a straight line.
Vibration Engineの鼓動
Vibration, heartbeat of the Engine.
速度増し上がってる高度
Speed increasing, rising altitude.
限界重力凌駕して上昇
Surpassing gravity limits, ascending.
開拓しまくってく Frontier
Opening up the Frontier like crazy.
旅立つ Roadster Only One
Departing Roadster, Only One.
Accel踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the Accel, spot on.
飛んでく日本医者？
Flying Japanese doctor? (Wait, maybe 'Nippon-sha' / Japanese car?)
一億馬力の重低音
100 million horsepower heavy bass.
火星のホテルで休憩所
Rest area at a hotel on Mars.
並んでそこ UFO 降り立つ宇宙 Station
Lining up there, UFO landing at the Space Station.
物語は継承
The story is inherited.
まるで旧約聖書
Just like the Old Testament.
この先の世紀も成長
Growing in the centuries ahead too.
生き延びて結果出す成功
Surviving and producing results, success!
以上、私たちFLOW GLOWでした！
That was us, FLOW GLOW!
こっから先も楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep enjoying the rest!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis
I'm infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll take you unraveled
Truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by chains, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of devastating force is coming
Out of the maze, feel my voltage rising and igniting fire
Snuff it out!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
And I'm singing a new gotcha
Locked and uploaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
And I'm singing a new gotcha
Locked and uploaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Justice is just like that
Don't care at all about diversion
I can't quit, never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out!
Make you fall down, make you make your last wish
Make you fall down and they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em make 'em fall down
Make you make your last wish
Make you make 'em fall down and they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em bound by a vow
Can't afford to warn desiring nevermaking sound
Think I need a new alibi to back away
Burning a mountain that followed us
And in the ashes fire
Snuff it out!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
And I'm singing a new gotcha
Locked and uploaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
And I'm singing a new gotcha
Locked and uploaded
Take 'em all out, Renegade!
Justice is just like that
Don't care at all about diversion
I can't quit, never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
The light goes out!
Woo!
Hah!
The light goes out!
空覚えで挑む人生ゲーム
Challenging the game of life with vague memories.
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following a heart full of excuses.
現実は端からfraudです
Reality is a fraud from the start.
取り憑かれるオーバーな自意識愛
Possessed by an excessive love of self-consciousness.
世渡り上手なあの娘はね
That girl who's good at getting by in the world...
二度と被った猫外せない
...can never take off the mask she put on.
痛みを知ってしまったマジシャン
The magician who learned what pain is,
手の内はまだ明かせない
can't reveal their hand just yet.
Yellow, Yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow, Yellow, looping from zero.
点滅するピリオド
A flashing period.
Yellow, Yellow 染まる赤い結晶
Yellow, Yellow, the red crystals are dyed...
たとえ
Even if
月に見放されても
we are abandoned by the moon,
Don't worry
私には私がついてる
I have myself with me.
酔いが覚めるまで
Until I sober up,
あと少しだけ
just a little longer.
真の愛 捉える残像
The afterimage capturing true love,
Slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を超え
Crossing over to the next season,
Blooming, Blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound.
Our time Yellow Yellow
Let it flow, Let it flow
ずっと Stay Gold
always Stay Gold.
Our time Yellow Yellow
Let it flow, Let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
Looking to the mirror
絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
the spider's thread is tangled.
It happens all the time
踊らされてたって構わない
I don't mind even if I was made to dance.
予期について
Following the expectations,
時を編んで明け暮れて
weaving time and spending my days.
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
things that never change forever.
Yellow Yellow 手を取り合えば
Yellow Yellow, if we hold hands,
そこに理由は要らない
we don't need a reason there.
Yellow Yellow 染まる赤い結晶
Yellow Yellow, the red crystal that is dyed.
As we should...
Wake up, make up, change your life
希望に目を光らせ
eyes shining with hope,
降りしきる運命や時勢ごと蹴散らせ
kick away the pouring fate and the times!
蜃気楼手にしたくて もがいて
Wanting to grasp the mirage, struggling...
Ready to go, oh!
Dive to get, there is no seven
終着地点は Heaven or Heaven?
is the terminal point Heaven or Heaven?
No time to wait 今だけを信じて
No time to wait, believe only in now,
最期のフィナーレまで 共に進め
until the final finale, let's advance together.
酔いが覚めるまで
Until I sober up,
あと少しだけ
just a little longer.
真の愛 捉える残像
The afterimage capturing true love,
Slow and steady wins the race
次の季節を超え
Crossing over to the next season,
Blooming, Blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound.
Our time Yellow Yellow
Let it flow, Let it flow
ずっと Stay Gold
always Stay Gold.
Our time Yellow Yellow
Let it flow, Let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
またね！
See ya!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
We are ReGLOSS! Bye bye!
Time to open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise
Got to break the wall and let me in
I know I was meant to be, living life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me, cause this is where my story all begins
Living it up like crazy, ready to break come at me
Gimme the win so easy, I can't get enough
Raise the bar no limit, having the good feeling
Get up and go let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me be a diva
I'm gonna raise the fever
Shaking up all the crowd
Making some noise when I'm not allowed
Living my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my anthem
Oh, oh, oh
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Oh, oh, oh
Pay attention, fool you once
Cause this is only the beginning
It's our Genesis
Coming to wreak some havoc
Have you realized this magic?
I'm embracing my madness
Can you hear it?
Whispers, banging down your window (I hear them)
Rumors, reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Whoa, whoa
Midnight, drawing to the dark side (Forever)
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
A mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our Genesis
Start the rave when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the funk commence, bet you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken
The rules can all be broken
I'm running on a rampage
The world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
Cuz they're gonna know me by name
Oh, oh, oh
This mark, won't miss, will
The future's in my hand
Oh, oh, oh
But they don't understand
Ba-ba-ba, ba-ba-ba...
Tell me how you like me now.
Yeah, yeah!
Let's celebrate the new year!
Come watch me, watch me, watch me!
Let your voice go,
let me show you how to lose control, yeah.
You got the key, unlock your mind.
Leave your worries behind.
Be outrageous,
the chaos is contagious!
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes,
feel the music start to rise.
Got to break the walls and let me in.
I know I was meant to be,
living life so fast and free.
Gonna keep your eyes on me,
'cause this is our beginning!
It's our genesis!
Whispers banging on your window,
rumors reaching a crescendo.
No humble beginning,
adapting, we're winning.
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Whoa!
Midnight, join me to the dark side.
Daylight, take me on a joyride.
My prime is my passion,
a mayhem in action!
I know what day it is!
This is our genesis!
You know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
君に届けたい
I want to reach you,
identity
my identity.
勝手に一歩を踏み出した
I took a step forward on my own accord.
おはよう こんばんは
Good morning, good evening.
各世界に叫んでみよう
Let's shout out to every world.
本日のライブでは
In today's live,
どれの自分を見せるの？
which version of myself should I show?
毎回こそ悩んで
Worrying about it every time,
好きな自分になれない
I can't become the self I like.
そしてある日誰かに言われた
And then, one day someone said to me,
「いらない言葉」なんかに迷っていた
I was getting lost in "unwanted words".
いつも作る笑顔失わないように
So I wouldn't lose the smile I always put on.
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided I won't betray expectations anymore.
あふれている雑音の中
Amidst the overflowing noise,
この声響けるか？
will this voice resonate?
心に宿る声を聞いてみよう
Let's listen to the voice dwelling in the heart.
これはずっと見せたい自分だから
Because this is the self I've always wanted to show.
集まった声たちが
The voices that gathered here,
ひとつになる identity
become one identity.
日々が過ぎてやっとスポットライトに
Days passed, and finally in the spotlight,
立てるけれど少しだけ怖くなった
I can stand tall, but I got a little scared.
でもね 一人じゃない
But you know, I'm not alone.
仲間たちがいるんだ
My friends are here.
家族みたいな絆で
With a bond like family,
違いが分かり合えた
we came to understand our differences.
それぞれの音が
Each distinct sound
互いを引き立て
complements the other,
ハーモニー奏でるから
creating a harmony.
手をつないで共に夢のその方へ
Hand in hand, together towards that dream.
精一杯歓声をあげましょう
Let's raise a cheer with all our might!
幸せを届けるんだ
We will deliver happiness.
どこにだって響けよ
Echo everywhere!
新しい舞台に飛び込んで
Diving into a new stage!
ここで全ての音色が
Here, all the tone colors...
クールのハーモニーになって
...become a cool harmony.
心の迷いが消えてゆく
The hesitation in my heart disappears.
これからずっと心 自分のままで
From now on, I'll always keep my heart true to myself.
集まった声たちが
The voices that have gathered here...
違っても揺るがないと信じて
...believe they won't waver, even if they are different.
一つになる Identity
Becoming one Identity.
Selamat pagi semuanya!
Good morning everyone!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
Selamat malam semuanya!
Good evening everyone!
また会う日まで！
Until the day we meet again!
我らエデンの星を統べる者
We are the ones who rule the star of Eden.
秘密結社... holoX！
Secret Society... HoloX!
でござる！
De gozaru!
機は熟した
The time is ripe.
2026年を待つ貴様ら！
You bastards waiting for 2026!
準備はいいか！
Are you ready?!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, look, Darkness.
能ある鷹は PON で隠す
A talented hawk hides it with a 'PON'.
脳に従え Instinct
Obey your brain, Instinct.
Not! ニンニン！
Not! Nin-nin!
サムライ Girl
Samurai Girl.
闇金しないけど
I don't do loan sharking, though.
フルベットでしょ
It's a full bet, right?
借金！借金！
Debt! Debt!
征服すれば OK
It's OK if we conquer it!
切り裂く赤字
Slashing through the deficit,
ジャキン！ジャキン！
Ch-ching! Ch-ching!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
You'll want to dance in the palm of evil.
ほらキミも 気づけばノリノリです
Look, you're already grooving before you know it.
どうしようもない
It can't be helped.
Don't show, No mind
堕ちてく運命なら
If it's a fated fall...
しょうがない
...it can't be helped.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's just repaint everything!
XとXとXとXが交差する真ん中で
In the center where X, X, X, and X intersect...
(X!!!)
Next, Next, Next 世界はもう始まってる
Next, Next, Next, the world has already begun.
じゃん！
Ta-da!
飛びな To be now
Fly now, to be now.
闇が呼ぶ方へ
Towards where the darkness calls.
暗黒のエクスデス
Dark Ex-Death.
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に
We shall repaint this chaotic world in HoloX colors...
塗り替えるのだ！
...completely!
皆の者、かかれ！
Everyone, attack!
Yes My Dark!!!
完璧漆黒・アブソルート・ダークネス・インフィニティ
Perfect Jet Black: Absolute Darkness Infinity.
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホークアイ！
Demon Eye: Hawk Eye!
お前もホロクターの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of the HoloXers!
コヨリニウムボム！
Koyorinium Bomb!
これでキミも こよにメロメロ～
With this, you'll be madly in love with Koyo~
疾風木葉斬り！
Gale Leaf Slash!
一刀両断 叩き斬る！
Cutting you in two with a single stroke!
どうしようもない
It can't be helped.
Don't show, No mind
堕ちてく運命なら
If it's a fated fall...
しょうがない
...it can't be helped.
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's just repaint everything!
括目せよ！
Bear witness!
Xと
X and...
...X and...
Xと
Xが交差する真ん中で
...X, in the center where they intersect...
Next, Next, Next 世界はもう始まってる
Next, Next, Next, the world has already begun.
じゃん！
Ta-da!
媚びな Complete now
Flatter, complete now.
つまり最後に
Which means, in the end...
笑うのは holoX です
...it's HoloX that laughs.
はい！我ら holoX！
Yes! We are HoloX!
ここから締めるぞ！
We're wrapping it up from here!
Run Back 'Round
Don't stop now
Up with the moonlight
Down in the streetlights
Lookin' for a spotlight
Makin' my move
I'm running
Whoa
行こう
Let's go
Days like a whirlwind
Don't stop comin'
Got me in a tailspin
What can I do?
Keep running
Whoa
行こう
Let's go
Lost and found
Back to where I started
I won't stay down
Trust me I can do it
I live life loud
Take it to the limit
So stand up proud
Now I'm gonna sing it
Run Back 'Round
It's a new beginning
I Run Back 'Round
Got to keep believing
I know where I'm going
I Run Back 'Round
Nothing's gonna stop me now
Oh, whoa, oh...
I'm gonna Run Back 'Round
Sparks on pavement
Dreams in the distance
Gotta be relentless
Faster than sound
Keep running
Whoa
行こう
Let's go
Locked and loaded
僕らは explosive
We are explosive
Swifter and lighter
明日もきっと brighter
Tomorrow will surely be brighter
Faster than lightning
About to get exciting
Come on everybody
It's a new day
Run Back 'Round
It's a new beginning
I Run Back 'Round
Got to keep believing
I know where I'm going
I Run Back 'Round
Nothing's gonna stop me now
Oh, whoa, oh...
I'm gonna Run Back 'Round
始まるよ
It's beginning
叶える
Fulfilling
Look at the dream this way
I'm gonna Run Back 'Round
心配ない
No worries
Goodbye
We got to come on
I'm gonna Run Back 'Round
Hololive! You guys ready?
To greet the new year?
Hell yeah!
No time to waste!
Let's get it started!
単純なフレーズでキャッチして
Catching it with a simple phrase,
苦難だらけの人生だけど
Even though life is full of hardships,
ズンポンポンにスラップして
Slap it to the beat (Zun-pon-pon)
感動しちゃおう
Let's get moved by it
Oh, oh, oh
Fly like a feather, soaring high
立ちはだかる壁なんて
The walls that stand in our way,
Bam! You're gonna knock out
Fly like a feather, soaring high
止まらないんじゃなくて
It's not that I won't stop,
止まれないんだ
It's that I can't stop.
Slap by Step で空中散歩
A walk in the sky, Slap by Step,
私なりで
In my own way.
隙あればその瞬間に完全掌握
If there's a gap, I'll seize total control in that instant,
沼にハマっちゃうぞ
You're gonna fall into the swamp (get addicted)!
One, two, three で深層心理
One, two, three, deep in your psychology,
クラッシュして
Crash it!
止まらない
I won't stop.
現実は厳しい外れの Life
Reality is a harsh, off-target life,
Full level 打ち抜いて
Shoot through at full level!
青く彩色 ニューダンスフロア
A blue-colored new dance floor.
どんなビートで平手打ちを
With what kind of beat will I slap?
距離も測りしないで 似合わないでしょう
Without even measuring the distance, it doesn't suit you, right?
Can't restart, can we slash?
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
すっ飛んじゃっても為せば成る それがセオリーさ
Even if we go flying, if there's a will there's a way. That's the theory.
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
地べた這い回して get ready
Crawl on the ground and get ready.
It's time for the show!
We're ignited and have no fear
Ready to break through
姿...
Appearance...
...形は
...and form.
違っても同じ思いだ
Even if we look different, our feelings are the same.
そうだから
That's why!
Step by stepで空中散歩 私なりで
Step by step, a mid-air stroll, in my own way.
吹き荒らば
If the wind blows wild.
その瞬間に完全掌握 沼にハマっちゃおう
In that moment, complete control. Fall into the swamp!
One, two, threeで深層心理 クラッシュして
With a one, two, three, crash into your deep psyche.
今すぐね
Right now,
私たちの色に染め上げた
dyed completely in our colors,
世界を見せる！
I'll show you the world!
皆様、今年の愛も...
Everyone, for your love this year...
...ありがとうですわ！
...thank you so much!
ホロライブはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！
Hololive is going to get even more exciting!
ずっと見てて！
Keep watching us forever!
来年もよろしくお願いします！
Please treat us well next year too!
See you next year!
皆さん、森カリオペです！
Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up!
Hololive English -Myth- comin' right at ya...
...for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね！
This year was super hype, huh!
来年もよろしく！
Treat us well next year too!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year.
You in?
Next up, Ina!
Wah!
Hello everyone!
This is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年すっごく楽しかったです！
This year was really fun!
来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
Please treat us well next year too!
Yeah, let's go!
Next is Kiara!
Kiwawa!
Kickerikick!
Kikkiriki!
小鳥遊キアラです！
I'm Takanashi Kiara!
キアラらしく盛り上げるぞ！
I'll hype it up Kiara-style!
Attention!
Please!
Come on!
Let's go!
Oh, right!
2026!
Let's go!
やってやりましょうか！
Shall we do this!
2026年もよろしく！
Treat us well in 2026 too!
Cool!
Alright!
Let's show 'em what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper truth or dare
The hands of fate play tug of war
But no one's keeping score
Set a course and beat the inertia
Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down but I'm all in
I'll play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now
While the wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread...
...I see what's up ahead
A wild chase!
A frantic pace!
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate!
Spin the wheel let's see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round jumping into the circle
Over and over a test of will
Oh the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
The thread's unbroken!
Called to life by flax and string
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I spin back round with every chance I get
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance
The staring dance
I spin this thread of fate with my own hands
La la la...
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoa yeah
After this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin', let's fly out
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハートキュンってバッピヤー
Heart goes kyun, bappiya!
Hyper Jumpin' 指の先まで
Hyper Jumpin', down to my fingertips
もっともっと
More and more
刺激が欲しいの
I want the thrill
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
子供じゃない はしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
I'm not a kid, but having fun is a better deal, right?
Take it up? から這い上がっていくテンション
Take it up? The tension crawling up from here
宵半ば 打ち返し捲るメンション
Mid-evening, firing back all the mentions
カオスを乗りこなして進むミッション
Riding the chaos to advance the mission
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating speed just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Unstoppable feelings take a running start
次元を超えて行こう
Let's transcend dimensions
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's jump around
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high, until we get even higher
陶酔的な
So euphoric
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sky
もっともっと
More and more
近付きたいの
I want to get closer
Woh oh oh...
ドキドキしたい ギミギミ愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme love
Woh oh oh...
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決クエスチョン
Attacking from an angle to solve the question
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェーンソー
A chainsaw that tears through the negativity
残れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session responding to the comments that remain
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリクション
Training my aim to snipe the friction
Listen nanana
気になるままに
Just as I'm curious
邪魔するノイズは 打ち消せ Bam bam bam
Erase the disturbing noise, bam bam bam
遊び足りないだけ
We just haven't played enough
味わい尽くして
Taste it all
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴飛ばせ Kicking
Kick it away, Kicking
Jump around Jump around
このまま僕らは旅をして
We continue our journey just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう
Let's transcend dimensions
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high, until we get even higher
超素敵な
It's super lovely
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea
もっともっと
More and more
近付きたいの
I want to get closer
Woh oh oh...
ドキドキしたい ギミギミ愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme love
Woh oh oh...
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
More and more, I want to fly higher
Hyper Jumpin' now
目を覚ませ
Wake up
目を凝らして
Look closely
夢から抜け出して
Slip out of the dream
世界が目撃する
The world will witness
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror,
心に宿っている
dwelling within my heart,
小さい光
is a small light.
さあ今も感じる
Come, I feel it even now,
どこかこの奥で
somewhere deep inside,
呼び覚ました
it has awakened.
忘れられない
Unforgettable,
浮かぶメモリ
memories float up.
今の自分になるその前に
Before I become who I am now...
果てのない
In an endless
迷路で迷い
maze, getting lost,
そして黄昏が
and then the twilight
落ちてくる
comes falling down,
どこまでも
forever and ever.
引き締める鎖がまた
The tightening chains again
身体を止めてた
stopped my body.
躊躇いを覚えてしまって
Learning to hesitate,
凍えてゆくの
I begin to freeze.
明日の向こう側には
On the other side of tomorrow,
未知なるエリア
lies an unknown area.
その境界線の先に待つのは
Waiting beyond that boundary line is...
15の創め
the beginning of 15.
目的わからず
Without knowing the purpose,
奈落の底へと
to the bottom of the abyss,
落ちてゆく
I keep falling.
時間さえ知らず
Unaware even of time,
時計の針の音
only the sound of the clock hands
だけが鳴る
rings out.
記憶に残り
Remaining in memory,
広がる海
the expanding sea.
届かぬ知らない森の中に
Inside a forest unknown and unreachable.
宇宙を越え
Crossing the universe,
逃げ場探して
searching for an escape.
そんな過去もまだ
Even such a past still
頭に響いている
echoes in my head.
解けない鎖を断ち
Cutting the chains that won't untie,
切れないままもがき
struggling while they remain unbreakable.
物語の始まり探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for the start of the story.
矛盾一度不可解な
A single contradiction, incomprehensible.
謎のようなことさ
It's like a riddle.
この身体の中で目覚めた
Awakened inside this body...
本当の姿
is my true form.
運命のカードが裏返る
The card of fate turns over.
真相へ
To the truth.
Oh my world
Fly
解き放った鎖が消え
The unleashed chains disappear,
進めると信じて
believing I can move forward.
新たな自分になって
Becoming a new self,
光の方へ
towards the light.
ついに辿り着いた
Finally arrived at
未知なるエリア
the unknown area.
その境界線を越える日が来た
The day has come to cross that boundary.
15の壁
The wall of 15.
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends I trust,
挑戦の狼煙を上げよう
let's raise the signal fire of challenge.
終わらない青春を
An unending youth!
偶然か羞恥心捨てて平然
Coincidence? Throw away shame, it's fine!
みんなで揃えば Good Job Job
If we're all together, Good Job Job!
行かなくちゃ
I gotta go.
零れ落ちて
It's spilling over,
青春感じている妄想
Delusions feeling the springtime of youth.
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show you how much I've grown.
リハは完璧 本番はもっと
Rehearsal was perfect, the real thing even more so!
全力で Hai Hai Huu!
With all our might, Hai Hai Huu!
大切な思い出
Precious memories,
たくさんあるけどね まだ
There are so many, but not yet...
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental.
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The biggest summer of this century begins!
Wow wow
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of imagination.
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run, overcome the wall of limits.
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers.
Yeah!
冷めた声に溺れたって
Even if drowned in cold voices,
微かな望らを手繰り寄せるように
As if reeling in a faint hope.
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments it's a letdown.
痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
Pain and yearning always fight.
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting by relying only on pride.
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself.
努力は報われる
Effort will be rewarded?
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let those who want to laugh, laugh.
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental.
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The biggest summer of this century begins!
Wow wow
反響が足りないもっともっと
The reaction isn't enough, more, more!
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it.
Ahhh!
想像の果てにある高み
The heights at the end of imagination.
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run, overcome the wall of limits.
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers.
Yeah!
Uuu... Uuu...
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our joined hands tight, not letting go.
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's go, to the dreaming sky.
Uuu... Uuu...
窓越しに見上げた
I looked up through the window,
とても小さな空
At a very small sky.
ここで出会えたのは
That we met here,
数えきれない奇跡
Is a countless miracle.
繰り返した一歩が
The repeated steps,
きらめきを繋いで
Connecting the sparkles,
星のような笑顔
Smiles like stars,
導いた
Guided us.
Day by day
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices become power.
Stage by stage
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
What each of us aims for here,
それぞれ描くもの
What each of us envisions,
それぞれ願った夢へ
To the dreams each of us wished for.
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our joined hands tight, not letting go.
一人ひとり違う色で描き出すときめき
The excitement drawn by each of us in different colors.
振り向くことなく真っすぐに
Straight ahead without looking back.
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, let's go, to the dreaming sky.
Uuu... Uuu...
笑いあったことや
Things we laughed about,
尽きることない話題
Topics that never run out,
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though we're full of memories...
浮気じゃなくて名前つけて保存
It's not cheating, it's 'Save As'.
どれも全部大事で言い切れる
I can declare that every single one is precious.
One, Two
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices become our power.
Three, Four
今日の賑やかすぎるくらい
Today is almost too lively,
笑顔がもう止まらない
and the smiles just won't stop.
想いは膨らんでいく
These feelings keep swelling up.
重ねた今 ぎゅっと噛み締めた
We cherished this overlapping moment so tightly.
一人一人違う声で歌えば広がる
If we sing with our unique voices, it spreads out.
風を感じたら真っ直ぐに
When you feel the wind, go straight ahead.
行くよ (行こう) 夢見る空へ
Let's go (Let's go) to the dreaming sky.
憧れで手を伸ばした
I reached out in admiration,
掴み取ったその光だ
and that is the light I grabbed.
いつの日か
Someday,
また誰かの憧れに変わる
it will turn into someone else's admiration.
繋ぐよ
We'll connect it.
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Without letting go of our joined hands,
一人一人違う色で描き出すときめき
we sketch out excitement in our own different colors.
出会った全てにありがとう
Thank you to everything we've met.
奇跡だって起こし続け ずっと側にいるよ
We'll keep making miracles happen and stay by your side forever.
行くよ (行こう) 夢見る空へ
Let's go (Let's go) to the dreaming sky.
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
はー、始まるだよ！
Haa, it's starting!
みんなお待たせ！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
We are GAMERS!!!!
楽しむ準備は？
Are you ready to have fun?
できてるよね？
You're all set, right?
せーの！
Ready, set!
We are GAMERS!!!!
ふーやー！
Fu-ya!
こんこんきつねの登場
The kon-kon fox has arrived.
白上ケモミミ白上フブキです
White hair, animal ears, I'm Shirakami Fubuki.
ツッコミ不在は間違いない
There's definitely no 'straight man' here.
君はすこん部に入部しなさい
You, join the Sukonbu club!
はい！Say！ (Yeah!)
Okay! Say! (Yeah!)
古今東西 ここはどこだい
All times and places, where is this?
CATじゃないし 特技はMC
I'm not a CAT, and my specialty is MCing.
歌ってみたより ゲームしてる
I play games more than I sing covers.
戦いが好き (Fooo!)
I love to battle! (Fooo!)
ミオしゃ！
Mio-sha!
ウチウチウチだよ 大神ミオだよ
It's me, me, me! It's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ大神ミオ
Black hair, animal ears, Ookami Mio.
ツッコんで止めます ゲーマーズのママ
I'll retort and stop them, I'm the Gamers' Mama.
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop, gera-gera.
つまり実はポンコツ？ (まあまあ！)
So actually I'm clumsy? (Well, sorta!)
こわしせつしちゃうこと？
Maybe I break things sometimes?
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future with Tarot cards.
ホラゲ... うわ！やりたくない！
Horror games... Uwa! I don't wanna do it!
4人揃えばまずは最強
When the four of us gather, we're the strongest.
君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
You play too, B-Dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ
Aim to clear and level up.
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too.
選択押してシミュレーション
Press select, simulation.
初見も古参も頼れるような
So newbies and veterans alike can rely on us,
いいゲームは楽しいね
good games are fun, aren't they?
G-A-M-E-R-S
We are GAMERS!!!!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
いくよ もぐもぐ猫又おかゆ
Let's go, munch munch, Nekomata Okayu.
おにぎりおにぎりはいどうぞ
Rice ball, rice ball, here you go.
きらきらふらふら自由な猫だもん
Sparkle sparkle, wander wander, I'm a free cat.
ふーん？そっか？僕で良くない？
Hmm? Is that so? Am I not good enough?
まったりゆっくり奏でるリズム
Laid back, slowly playing rhythm.
全肯定するおかゆイズム
Affirming everything, that's Okayu-ism.
全肯定？肯定？OK?
Total affirmation? Affirmation? OK?
毎日僕と一緒
Every day together with me.
ころね！
Korone!
おはよー！ゆびゆび Wow Wow
Good morning! Yubi yubi, Wow Wow!
パン屋こねこね 戌神ころね
Bakery knead-knead, Inugami Korone.
犬種キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel.
長いね ちょっとけど覚えとけ
It's a bit long, but remember it!
訛りイントネーション 割れるリアクション
Accent intonation, blown-out reaction.
まずは指を捧げてくれる？
First, will you offer up your fingers?
配信中？分かったなぁ...
Streaming? I get it...
はーい！摂取！
Okaaay! Confiscated!
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering my favorite retro games.
4人揃えばまず最強
If the four of us gather, we're the strongest!
運が悪ければ即回収
If our luck is bad, it's an instant game over!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Train your aim and shoot!
今日は何プレイしよ？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll heal your heart!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
This dungeon is exciting, isn't it?
耐久っていうかやめられないだって
It's an endurance run, or rather, I just can't stop...
ゲームが好きなんだもん
Because I love games!
突然ですが ボーナスチャレンジの時間です
Suddenly, it is time for a Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして
Respond with a loud voice...
高得点を狙いましょう
...and let's aim for a high score!
Are you ready?
Say KON-KON!
KON-KON!
Say MION-MION!
MION-MION!
Say MOGU-MOGU!
MOGU-MOGU!
Say YUBI-YUBI!
YUBI-YUBI!
Say KON-KON!
KON-KON!
Say MION-MION!
MION-MION!
Say MOGU-MOGU!
MOGU-MOGU!
Say YUBI-YUBI!
YUBI-YUBI!
4人揃えばまず最強
If the four of us gather, we're the strongest!
上手くいかなくてもコンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, we'll continue!
エンドロールまで諦めない
We won't give up until the end roll!
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートを攻略しちゃう
We'll capture your heart!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choice, simulation!
初見も古参も頼れるやっぱ
Newcomers and veterans alike can rely on us!
ね ゲームは楽しいね
Hey, games are fun, aren't they?
We are GAMERS!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった
And thus, the curtain closed on 2025.
生まれたてのドキドキを
Let the newfound excitement...
響かせよう
...resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
キラメキに乗って
Ride on the sparkle!
Yeah!
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember the first song?
懐かしいね
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
私 声が震えていた
My voice was trembling back then.
恥ずかしい
How embarrassing.
あの日から続く未来は
The future continuing from that day...
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
...is the today we seized together with everyone.
もっと もっと
More and more,
もっと もっと 加速するハート
more and more, my heart accelerates.
一緒に (行くよどこまでも)
Together (We'll go anywhere!)
Are you ready?
準備はOK？
Are preparations OK?
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door to your dreams!
1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを
Let the newfound excitement...
響かせよう
...resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
ここにいるよ
I am right here,
見つけてくれたから
because you found me.
君に会いたくて
I wanted to see you,
やって来たんだ
so I came all this way.
みんなで歌を
Let's sing together,
終わらないメロディ
an unending melody.
キラメキに乗って
Ride on the sparkle!
届いてるかな
Is it reaching you?
私の声
My voice.
ハッキリと
Clearly.
届けたいのは
What I want to deliver...
君に笑顔
...is a smile to you.
そのスマイル
That smile.
理想の遠さに
At how far the ideal was,
悔しくて
I was frustrated.
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We laughed and cried with everyone, didn't we?
ギュッと ギュッと
Tightly, tightly,
ギュッと ギュッと 全て抱きしめて
tightly, tightly, embrace everything.
一緒に (行こうどこまでも)
Together (Let's go anywhere!)
Are you ready?
準備はOK？
Are preparations OK?
進め 希望の道を
Advance down the road of hope!
1, 2, 3 キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
好きな気持ち
My feelings of love...
カラフルに奏でたいな
...I want to play them colorfully.
最高の場所 最高の皆と
In the best place, with the best everyone,
ここにいるよ
I am right here.
幻なんか
It's not an illusion...
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness,
重ねてくハーモニー
We layer our harmonies.
キラメキ纏って
Clad in sparkles,
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep on singing.
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep on dancing.
そんな願いは わがままもいいでしょう
Such a wish... it's fine to be selfish about it, right?
だって楽しすぎて
Because it's just too much fun,
もう止まらない
I can't stop anymore!
輝くステージで
On this shining stage,
もっともっと
More and more,
ずっと
Forever!
嬉しい楽しい愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, lovely... words alone aren't enough.
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I have worries, but...
ここにいるよ
I am right here.
私 ここにいるよ
I am right here!
君と同じ世界を
The same world as you...
見つめて
Gazing at it.
キラメキライダー
Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキも響かせよう
Let's make this newborn excitement resonate.
最高の時間
The greatest time,
最高の仲間と
with the greatest friends!
ここにいるよ
We are right here.
見つけてくれたから
Because you found us.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
We came here because we wanted to see you.
みんなで歌おう
Let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ
An ending melody.
キラメキに乗って
Riding the sparkles,
キラメキ纏って
Clad in sparkles!
Yeah!
2025年はあと少し！
2025 is almost over!
みんな盛り上がってる？
Is everyone hyped up?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This is the Countdown Live!
あれ？あれれ？
Huh? Wait a sec?
コメントの流れ、なんか少なくない？
Aren't the comments flowing a bit slow?
まだまだ足りないんじゃないのー！？
Isn't it still not enough!?
いくぞー！
Let's go!
このこのこのこの
You, you, you, you...
推し変は許しません
I won't forgive you if you switch stans.
私だけに尽くしてね
Devote yourself only to me, okay?
私だけに一筋
Be straight and true only to me.
炭水化物抜きとかやだやだ摂取！
Cutting carbs? No way, no way, intake!
尊重！
Respect!
赤巻紙！
Red scroll paper!
ちょちょちょ 誰も
Wait wait wait, no one...
よそ見したら ぷんぷんぷん！めっ！
If you look away, I'll be angry! Bad!
メロメロメロメロ 恋心
Mero mero mero mero, love-struck heart.
膨らむ胸
My chest is swelling.
もっとアップップ
Zoom in closer, up up up.
浮気心とか
Cheating thoughts and such,
持たないでしょ
You don't have them, right?
目移りはだめ
Looking elsewhere is forbidden.
本当いいやいいや
Really, no, no.
いつも見てみて
Always look, look at me.
わがまま言ってる？
Am I being selfish?
あなたが推してくれる
Because you support me,
愛情の全開
With your love at full throttle,
私は支える
I will support you.
栄養素！
I'm your nutrient!
らびゅらびゅらびゅち
Love you, love you, love you-chi.
四六時中夢中
Obsessed twenty-four seven.
とってもとってもとってもとっても
Very, very, very, very,
愛して欲しい
I want you to love me.
ハピハピハピピ 最上級はぎゅはぎゅ
Happy happy hapipi, the highest level is a hug-hug.
やっぱりやっぱりやっぱりやっぱり
After all, after all, after all, after all,
ハッキリハッキリハッキリハッキリ
Clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly.
わかってるでしょ ピコピコ
You understand, right? Pico pico.
気持ちのバロメーター
My feeling's barometer,
超上がる
Is super rising!
（もっと推して推して！）
(Support me more, support me!)
（推し通し！）
(Push through with your support!)
もう本当に本当に本当に本当に？
Really, really, really, really?
わかってね？
Understand?
おーいみんな！
Hey everyone!
ここまでついてこれてる？
Are you keeping up so far?
このあともこの調子で
Let's keep this energy going after this too,
いくよー！
Here we go!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Urya oi! Urya oi!
うりゃうりゃうりゃうりゃ！
Urya urya urya urya!
ちょっと待って なんで他の子褒めるの？
Wait a minute, why are you praising other girls?
よそ見 疑惑 発令中
Suspicion of looking away is currently in effect.
私の疑問 気になってるでしょ？
You're curious about my question, right?
ありえない！ありえない！
Impossible! Impossible!
ぺんぺん！他の子にちょちょちょだけ
Pen pen! Just a little bit with other girls...
よそ見したよね？嘘まじ無理！
You looked away, didn't you? Lies are seriously impossible!
浮気心じゃ私を尊大
With a cheating heart, treating me arrogantly...
指切りしてよ！針千本！
Pinky promise! Or swallow a thousand needles!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
このこのこのこの...
This, this, this, this...
絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対！
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely!
お願いね！
Please!
このこのこのこの！
This, this, this, this!
このこのこのこのこのこのこの！
This, this, this, this, this, this, this!
銀河の果てまで推してほしい！
We want you to support us to the ends of the galaxy!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future.
あの夢 手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream.
それぞれ違った心で
With our different hearts,
走れば
if we run...
どこ見ても真っ暗な
No matter where I looked, it was pitch black,
場所に芽生えてた
but something sprouted in that place.
ほんの小さな希望に
By just a tiny hope,
この瞳 奪われた
my eyes were captivated.
不安で揺れる心を
Letting my heart, shaking with anxiety,
うまく宇宙に逃がして
skillfully escape into space,
ほんの小さな勇気を
I was squeezing out
振り絞っていたよ
just a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字
I delete the word 'give up'
Deleteして進む
and move forward.
苦しい時も
Even in painful times,
もう私は
I am no longer
一人じゃないから
alone, so...
だからもっと夢 追いかけたい
That's why I want to chase the dream more!
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop!
想像を超えてく
Surpassing imagination,
世界 見せてあげる
I'll show you the world!
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it.
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you regret it.
それぞれ違った心で
With our different hearts,
走れば
if we run...
仮想の空に輝く
Shining in the virtual sky,
眩しい想いは
these dazzling feelings
見たこともない光を
will deliver a light I've never seen before
リアルに届けるよ
to reality.
いつも聞こえるエールは
I capture the cheers I always hear
ここにキャプチャして
right here,
また新しい光を
and I start wanting to search
探したくなるよ
for a new light again.
君の笑顔を
I save your smile
保存して進む
and move forward.
悲しい時に
When I'm sad, I look back at it,
見返すよ
because strength wells up.
力が湧くから
Because strength wells up.
胸を張って夢 追いかけたい
I want to chase the dream with my head held high.
奇跡のストーリー
Let's create this miraculous story
一緒に作ろう
together.
終わらない夢を
An unending dream...
誰一人欠かせない
No one is indispensable.
愛が埋まったこの世界
In this world filled with love,
それぞれ違った心で
with our different hearts,
彩れ
Color it in!
悲しい時も
Even in sad times,
寂しい時も
even in lonely times,
信じ合えるものがある
there is something we can believe in together.
忘れずに
Don't forget,
この鼓動
I want to keep ringing
鳴らし続けたい
this heartbeat.
終わらない世界に
In the unending world,
溢れ出すよ
they overflow...
笑顔たち
these smiles.
憧れの舞台 立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams.
まっすぐ輝きたい
I want to shine straight and true.
時に涙して
Sometimes shedding tears,
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future.
あの夢 手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream.
踏み出そう
Let's step forward,
奇跡の一歩を
taking that miraculous first step.
息切らして夢 追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase the dream.
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop!
想像を超えてく
Surpassing imagination,
世界 見せてあげる
I'll show you the world!
アクセスしてみたい
I want to try accessing it.
後悔なんてここにない
Regret doesn't exist here.
それぞれ違った心で
With our different hearts,
作るの
we create it!
みんな、コークは持ったかな？
Does everyone have their Coke?
持ちました！乾杯するー！
Got it! Let's toast!
こらこら！
Hey, hey!
あー！早いよラプちゃん！
Ah! Too early, Lap-chan!
避けるな！
Don't dodge!
当たるぅ！
It's gonna hit!
年越しのタイミングでみんなで乾杯ってするんだよ！
We're all supposed to toast at the moment the year changes!
やだやだ！もう喉カラカラ！
No way! I'm already super thirsty!
楽しみだね！
Can't wait, right?
ね？みこさん？…みこさん？
Right, Miko-san? ...Miko-san?
いや～いいライブだったね～
Man, that was a great concert.
おつかれ～
Good work~
イェ～イ
Yaay.
この後どうする？
What do we do after this?
ご飯食べる？
Want to get food?
いや、どこも混んでるんじゃない？
Nah, everywhere's probably crowded, right?
確かに。
True.
もう帰りますかね。
Guess we'll just head home.
あ、運転手さん、まっすぐね。
Ah, driver, go straight please.
ブゥー。
(Grunt)
おい！
Hey!
お前ら！
You guys!
何 帰ってんだ！
Why are you going home?!
乾杯！乾杯！
Toast! Toast!
フブちゃん達がついて来てる！
Fubu-chan and the others are following us!
あらあらフブさん寂しくなっちゃったのかね？
Oh my, Fubu-san must have gotten lonely without us.
待てー！
Waaait!
なんか怒ってない？
Doesn't she seem angry?
え？
Eh?
あ、やばい。
Ah, crap.
あの悪戯バレたかな。
She might have found out about that prank.
やりすぎだったかも～！
We might have overdone it~!
やばいかも！
This might be bad!
運転手さんごめん！
Driver, sorry!
おっ、おお～
Whoa, whoa~
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞ！
I'll escape with Miko's driving technique!
ワオ！ワオ！
Wow! Wow!
あ！来た！
Ah! They're here!
危ねぇ！
Watch out!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
フブさんごめんて！
Fubu-san, I said sorry!
もう悪戯しないから！
I won't pull any more pranks!
だめだよみこみこ、反省しなさい。
No good, MikoMiko. Reflect on your actions.
お前も共犯だろうが！
You were an accomplice too!
何の話だよ～。
What are you talking about~
二人ともこれ持って。
You two, hold this.
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost the New Year!
乾杯！
Cheers!
あけましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
わんわんわんわんわん！
Wan wan wan wan wan!
今年もよろしくね！
Let's have a great year too!
ぷはぁー！
Puh-aaah!
ごくごくいっぱい！
Gulp gulp, full up!
そういえば、悪戯ってなんなの？
By the way, what was the prank?
あ、それね。
Ah, that.
フブキさんのへそ、増やしたんだよ。
I increased Fubuki-san's belly buttons.
恐怖！
The horror!
このあとは、コカ・コーラと一緒に
Up next, with Coca-Cola,
スペシャルライブステージ！
it's a Special Live Stage!
イェーイ！
Yeaaah!
そうさずっと僕らの軌跡が
Yes, so that our miracle
途切れないように歌うんだ
Will never be broken, we sing
もっと高く
Higher,
大きな声で
With a louder voice
聞こえてた何かが始まるサイン
I could hear it, the sign that something is starting
集まって気づけば鼓動奏でた
Gathering together, before we knew it, our heartbeats played a tune
夢に見るだけじゃもう足りないでしょ
Just dreaming about it isn't enough anymore, right?
君を待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you
楽しい予感にほら飛び乗っちゃえばいい
Just jump into that fun premonition, come on
トキメキは止められないから
Because this excitement can't be stopped
明日を連れていくよ光の真ん中
I'll take tomorrow with me, into the center of the light
夢の先へ羽ばたける
We can fly to what lies beyond the dream
勇気は君の願い
Courage is your wish
みんなで繋いだこの奇跡が
This miracle we connected together
途切れないように歌うんだ
We sing so it won't be broken
もっと高く
Higher,
大きな声で
With a louder voice
答えとか理屈に惑わされて
Confused by answers and logic
彷徨っても戻ってこれる場所があったんだ
Even if I wandered, there was a place I could return to
自由な道ゆく僕らの旅
Our journey goes along a free path
願いだけが道標だよ
Only our wishes are the signposts
夢の色が変わっても変わらないメロディー
A melody that doesn't change even if the color of the dream does
君のために僕らのために
For you, and for us
歌おう
Let's sing
そうさきっと僕らの奇跡は
Yes, surely our miracle
終わらないよ涙さえ
Will not end, even tears
きっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn them into a chance
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in me
どこへだって飛び出して行こう
Let's jump out to anywhere
もっと遠く
Farther away
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, to you who we haven't met yet,
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
we have so many things we want to tell you.
浮かれた今は
This festive moment is...
当たり前なんかじゃない
...not something to take for granted.
翼を広げ サインだ
It's a sign to spread your wings.
とぼう
Let's fly!
Take my heart 連れて行くよ
Take my heart, I'll take you with me,
光の真ん中
to the center of the light,
夢の先へ
to beyond the dream.
羽ばたける 勇気は
The courage to flap my wings...
君の願い
...is your wish.
みんなで繋いだ この奇跡が
This miracle we connected together...
途切れないように 歌うんだ
...I'll sing so it doesn't break.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Higher, with a louder voice,
僕らの未来の音
the sound of our future...
どこまでも響け
...echo everywhere.
Prism Melody
Won't you just forget about the past
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan apinya takkan padam
Ensure the fire won't go out
Ditemani cahaya
Accompanied by the light
To hear what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can all stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Melayang, mimpi 'kan kau layang
Fly, you will fly your dreams
Kau cari, teriakan
You search, shout it out
La la la la la
Takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan apinya takkan padam
Ensure the fire won't go out...
Gerakkan, murnikan hati
Move, purify the heart
To hear what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can all stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Melayang, mimpi 'kan kau layang
Fly, you will fly your dreams
Kau cari, teriakan
You search, shout it out
La la la la la
Takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
So go and run so far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La la la la la
Be who you meant to be
がんばろう！
Let's do our best!
Pada akhirnya
In the end
Semua kan baik saja
Everything will be fine
Hadapkan pandanganmu
Face your gaze forward
Tajam lurus ke depan
Sharp straight ahead
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Bentang sayap kau cari
Spread your wings and search
Cahaya kan...
The light will...
La la la...
Takkan sendiri
Won't be alone
Just look around and see, it's so incredible
So many smiles in the sea of lights
Take one step with me, and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment I can dream with you
Every miracle we hope for might come true
We come together reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices join in harmony tonight
We're gonna shine bright together
We're all for one (Let's sing!)
All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one (Let's sing!)
All for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day
The rest of our lives (Hey!)
Set the things in motion
Get ready start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
I hope you feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're here together finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
I hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear
So glad to be here together
We're all for one (Let's sing!)
All for one
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's all for one (Let's sing!)
All for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night
The rest of our lives (Hey!)
Raise up your hands and sway
Your light will lead our way
We're shining all for one
All for one
Building a memory, a joy and a hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road
Feel the music and your passion is on
We're here right now so let the good times roll
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you, if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
One, two, three, four, five!
When our voices join in harmony tonight
We're gonna shine bright together
We're all for one (Let's sing!)
All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one (Let's sing!)
皆さん、明けましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
ReGLOSSです！
We are ReGLOSS!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブDEV_ISコラボステージです！
From here on, it's the Hololive DEV_IS collab stage!
聴いてください、FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS！
Please listen to FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS!
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン
Mounted V8 engine,
第7感持ってる原人
a primitive man with the seventh sense.
Rockするこの世界と全人類
Rocking this world and all humanity,
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
changing the game with these five.
唸る4輪発射せよ
Roaring four wheels, fire!
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo.
操る2台のTurntable
Controlling two Turntables,
取る1番ここGround zero
taking number one, here is Ground Zero.
Aye リスク超えて挑戦
Aye, challenge beyond the risk.
チャンスもセットだ当然
Chance comes as a set, of course.
登り上げる頂点
Ascending to the summit,
座布団積んでく昇天
piling up cushions, ascending to heaven.
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Boarding the FG ROADSTER.
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces, gathering of espers.
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names in history,
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
leaving the trailing cars far behind.
今高速で
Now at high speed,
ぶち抜けていく大気圏
breaking through the atmosphere.
エンジンからジェットの炎
Jet flames from the engine,
揺れている回帰炎
the backdraft is flickering.
眼下に広がる大地を
The vast land spreading below,
超えていく回帰線
crossing the tropic line.
バックミラーにBig Blueが映っているIBM
Big Blue is reflected in the rearview mirror, IBM.
打ち上げ台から飛んでく
Flying from the launch pad,
うちら世代
our generation.
この燃料朽ち果てないです
This fuel won't run out,
銀河で寿司食べたい
I want to eat sushi in the galaxy.
見えてるデカいビジョン
A huge vision is visible,
燃えてるメンバー一同
all members are burning.
ただいま現在進行形
Currently in progress,
超えてく世界規模
exceeding global scale.
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It should come true, won't stop.
心臓がモンスター
My heart is a monster.
Aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光るTESLA Roadster
Shining TESLA Roadster,
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Instincts awakening,
青い炎
blue flame.
BFF let's go out, so get in the car
ゼロから宇宙まで囚われず
From zero to space, unrestrained.
走るFG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER,
唸るBooster
roaring booster.
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me
Now chase me.
In my chase me...
明けましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たちFLOW GLOWが
From here on, we, FLOW GLOW,
ReGLOSS先輩のフィーリングラデーションをカバーさせていただきます！
will cover ReGLOSS-senpai's "Feeling Gradation"!
二子ちゃんが来たー！
Niko-chan is here!
青春に行くぞ！ しょっぴしょー！
Let's go for youth! Shoppisho!
エンジン全開 Let's go!
Engine full throttle, let's go!
さあ、待ちきれない！
Come on, I can't wait!
う～、ヴィヴィ！
Ooh, Vivi!
私の元に、おいで！
Come to me!
My heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
A new chapter unraveled,
Changes to show time
さあ早変わり Stage show time
Now, a quick change, stage show time.
全然悪くない Imagination
Not bad at all, imagination.
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The mist in my vision is clear.
悲しみに別れを告げ
Saying goodbye to sadness.
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing the sour and sweet into the air,
滲む空インクは薔薇色
the bleeding sky ink is rose-colored.
どれだけ上手く見せようとしても
No matter how well I try to show off,
君がいなければ何の意味もない
without you, it has no meaning.
かすり傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion that won't even get scratched.
針の落ちないレコードのさ
Records that don't fall off.
たった今 予期せぬ追い風
Just now, an unexpected tailwind.
Come on let's roll
颯爽と吹き荒れる向かい風にも
Even the dashing headwind,
心靡かせて
let our hearts flutter.
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future.
Flying just started alright, restart line (Hey!)
ときめいてしまえば
If you get excited,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
open zones will expand in a flash.
ひとつひとつ全てがドラマ
Every single one is a drama.
待ちわびた daybreak, restart line (Hey!)
I've been waiting for daybreak, restart line (Hey!)
変わる変わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama of changing colors,
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
filling up feeling gradation.
飛び出して You raise me up
Jump out, you raise me up.
恐れるものはない Restart the life (Hey!)
There's nothing to fear, restart the life (Hey!)
綺麗な朝焼けが
A beautiful morning glow
透明な明日を照らすよ
will light up the transparent tomorrow.
Restart the life (Hey!)
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は！
The last song is...
Our Bright Parade！
Our Bright Parade!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Parade, Parade, Parade
輝くんだよ
It shines bright.
呼び合う声を合図に
Signaled by voices calling each other.
Parade, Parade, Parade！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく スタートは何度だって
We go searching, we can start over any number of times.
ただ 独り言続いた
I just kept talking to myself.
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted to begin.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
A light lit up in the distant darkness.
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That name was too dazzling.
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Those memories were too gentle.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I wanted to get closer, so I reached out my hand.
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, we connected.
ほら 今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now the lost children have become "us".
Parade, Parade, Parade！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
It shines!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along your frustrations and your beloved feelings.
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき日差し
A humble prayer is light, an endless sunshine.
君も見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
You can be proud of what you found too.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade！
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
まだ頼りない横顔 歌おう
Let's sing with our still unreliable profiles.
恥ずかしくなんてないよ
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary that no one can solve.
いつかまた会えるおまじない
A magic spell to meet again someday.
あの日ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that began from zero that day.
数えきれない言の葉
Countless words.
数えるような想いじゃないさ
It's not a feeling that can be counted.
ほら 今 僕らをひとつと呼ぼう
Look, let's call "us" one now.
Parade, Parade, Parade！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
美しいんだよ
It's beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
In the fleeting moment we forgive each other, the night sparkles.
雨 晴れ カレイド またとない空
Rain, sun, kaleidoscope, a sky like no other.
相応しい旅路とは
A fitting journey is...
君とあることさ
being with you.
君とあることなんだ
It truly is being with you.
ただいまを聞けば おかえりって叫ぶよ
If I hear "I'm home", I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that obvious?
Parade, Parade, Parade！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
It shines!
暗がりを満たすのは君だ 僕だ
The one filling the darkness is you, it's me!
Parade, Parade, Parade！
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
It shines!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along your frustrations and your beloved feelings.
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき日差し
A humble prayer is light, an endless sunshine.
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, it's a wonderful start.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade！
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade！
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
キャスト
Cast
セットリスト
Setlist
この後はもう1本グランプリ！
Coming up next: The 'One More' Grand Prix!
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Please continue to support Hololive Production in 2026!